仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  冰蓝  吃货丁小七  glida  洗七里
翻译:  MsFool  小泡椒  芝小士  亲爱的小饭
校对:  赛太公帅到不需要道歉
时间轴:  三水
后期:  灰灰是菇凉    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第七集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
好啊
Howdy!
欢迎来到感恩节乡村欢宴
Welcome to the Thanksgiving country jamboree!
邓菲一家都来了
We got the whole Dunphy clan,
克莱尔  菲尔  卢克  艾丽克斯和
Claire, Phil, Luke, Alex and --
这位开心的农场工人是谁
well, and who is this happy farmhand?
我是杰瑞
I'm Jerry.
杰瑞以前住我们隔壁
Jerry used to live next door.
受一场残酷的离婚折磨几年了
He's been going through a brutal divorce for years,
本来他要一个人过感恩节
and he was gonna spend Thanksgiving alone.
菲尔觉得应该让他
Phil thought it'd be a good idea
跟一个运转良好的快乐家庭度过今天
if he spent the day with a happy, functional family.
我们找不到那样的家庭  所以他跟我们过
We couldn't find one, so he's coming with us.
海莉呢
So, where's Haley?
她跟雷纳在一起
She's with Rainer.
他们最近经常见面  这挺好的
They've been seeing a lot of each other, which is great.
有趣的是  开始他是我的朋友
Funny thing is, he was my friend first,
但现在我都见不到他了  也见不到海莉
but now I never see him. Or Haley.
-菲尔  -大家就是这么想啊
- Phil. - It's what everybody's thinking.
我不想让大家如履薄冰
I don't want people walking on eggshells
因为他本来是我朋友  但现在我都见不到他
'cause he was my friend first, but now I never see him.
或是海莉
Or Haley.
我一周只被允许探望一次我的孩子们
I'm only allowed to see my children once a week.
我都跟他们不太熟
I hardly know them.
克拉克是数学俱乐部的主席
Oh, well, Clark's head of the math club,
缇娜成了个小荡妇
and Tina's turned into a bit of a slut.
谢谢你的新资讯
Thanks for the update.
-他们来了  -好啊
- Okay, there they are! - Hi!
在周日的下午  你们看起来真像
Don't y'all look as pretty as a peach pie
桃子派一样动人啊
on a Sunday afternoon?
我的老天啊
For the love of God,
今天真心不想见到这样
this is the last thing I need today.
好啊  风味哥[歌手]  怎么戴这么大一块表
Hey, Flavor Flav, what's up with the giant watch?
都怪我的医生烦人
It's my doctor being a pain in the butt.
一次血压过高  我就得
One high reading, I got this thing
整天戴着这玩意儿测血压
taking my blood pressure all day.
等等  你没事吧
Wait, are you okay?
有事  他得戒掉雪茄和垃圾食品
No. He needs to quit cigars and the terrible food.
上周我抓到他在车库里
Last week, I caught him in the garage
偷吃波兰香肠
eating a Polish sausage.
男人在热水器后方做的事
What a man does behind his water heater
是他自己的私事
is his own business.
别担心  我自有妙方
Don't worry about it. I've got it beat.
我的秘诀是这样
Here's my trick.
这玩意儿开始叫时
As soon as this thing goes off,
我就开始唱70年代的慢摇滚
I start singing sweet '70s soft rock
使自己放松
to mellow myself out.
这些歌是万能的
Those songs could do anything.
席尔和克罗夫开始唱
Seals and Crofts came on,
活跃于70年代的美国慢摇滚团体
女人的喇叭裤脱光光
lady's bell bottoms came off.
-好吧  -大家好啊
- Well... - Hey, y'all.
有人想吃油炸玉米饼吗
Anybody have a hankering for a hush puppy?
天啊
Oh, geez.
* 夏日微风 *
* Summer breeze *
该团体的歌曲《Summer Breeze》
* 让我舒爽 *
* Makes me feel fine *
这到底是在搞什么鬼
What is going on here?
* 吹动茉莉花 *
* Blowing through the jas- *
这是乡村感恩节欢宴嘛
It's a Thanksgiving jamboree!
我们有一捆捆干草  苹果榨汁机
We have bales of hay. We have a cider press.
甚至还有油炸火鸡
Ooh, we're even deep-frying a turkey.
你同意这一切吗
And you're on-board with this?
是啊  这可是乡村乐趣
Yes! Come on, it's good country fun.
不
No.
对小卡来说  也许有趣
For Cam, maybe.
怎么回事  他打你了吗
What is happening? Is he hitting you?
没有
No.
你做了什么错事  对吧
You did something, didn't you?
你做了
You did!
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
我很喜欢这一切  好吗
I'm -- I'm loving this, okay?
准头需要练习
That takes practice.
不  除非你告诉我你做了什么  否则我不走
No, I am not leaving here until you tell me what you did.
要来一梅森玻璃瓶的夏敦埃酒吗
Can I get you a mason jar of Chardonnay?
妥妥的
Giddy up.
学生会主席先生
Mr. Student Council President,
你是否看过了我关于
have you had a chance to look at my proposal
更新网络暴力准则的建议
updating the honor code to address cyber-bullying?
稍等一下
One second.
你为什么要那么叫我
Why would you call me that?
卢克莫名其妙在主席竞选中赢了我
Luke somehow beat me in the election for president,
而我到现在还无法释怀
and I still can't get over it.
毫不夸张地说  人类离骑在马背上
Not to be hyperbolic, but humans are a decade away
跟人猿战斗的年代已经不远了
from fighting apes on horseback.
你是想告诉我
You're trying to tell me
这里一切都很正常吗
that there's absolutely nothing weird going on here?
你穿的就像乡村背景的
You are dressed like a character
《人鼠之间》加强版的角色
out of "It's Raining Mice and Men".
我完全不知道你在说啥
I don't know what you're talking about, okay?
我享受这场派对可是多过享受
I am enjoying this more than a farm animal
某次看残疾农场动物在做...
missing a limb engaged in...
"爱"做的事呢
some sort of activity.
好吧  我做了点坏事
Okay, I did something bad.
我就知道
I knew it.
非常坏的事
Yeah, yeah, something real bad.
我需要先把小卡哄开心了才敢告诉他
I need Cam in a good mood before I tell him.
你出轨了吗  听起来像是出轨了
Is it infidelity? If feels like infidelity.
-我不能说  -米奇尔
- I can't say. - Hey, Mitchell?
轮到你来体会搅乳桶的炽热了
It's your turn to feel the burn on the churn!
那我最好脚底抹"油"  冲去搅"黄油"啦
Well, then I "butter" get over there.
好啊  来吧
Okay, come on!
你好  德怀特
Hey, Dwight.
女士你好
Ma'am.
所以他们这么刚好家里有
So, did they just happen to have this costume
这件符合你大小的制服吗
lying around in your size?
虽然很诡异  但确实如此
Weirdly, they did.
不不不  德怀特
Whoa, whoa, whoa. No, Dwight
下周有本赛季最重要的比赛之一
has one of the most important games of the season next week
我不能让你把他弄生病了
and I can't have you getting him sick.
我的单核细胞增多症已经好了
Yeah, I'm over the mono.
但还是有可能有传染性
But it could still be contagious,
而我想到一个适合你的有趣造型
and I have a fun costume idea for you.
打扮成旧时代的银行抢匪怎么样
How about being an old-timey bank robber?
要在警长赶到之前把脸遮住
You gotta cover that face before the marshal gets to town.
发生什么事了
Hi! Oh, what happened?
没什么  就是做了个韩式激光换肤
Oh, nothing, just a Korean laser peel.
超级疼  但是皮肤新生出来以后
Hurt like hell, but once the skin regenerates,
能让我这双赚钱的手年轻十岁
it's gonna take ten years off these money makers.
她来了
Hey! There she is.
多谢你送她过来
Thanks for dropping her off.
其实  雷纳的女儿跟她妈在一起
Uh, actually, Rainer's daughter is with her mom,
所以我邀请他来跟我们一起过感恩节
so I invited him to spend Thanksgiving with us.
我超爱这个乡村主题
I am loving this country theme!
让我想起当初给塔尔萨市的十二新闻台
This reminds me of when I worked for Newscenter Twelve
工作的日子  除了这里没有刻薄的醉汉
in Tulsa, except no one here's bitter and drunk.
我就怕你待在这里会觉得格格不入
Gosh, I would hate for you to feel weird, though,
毕竟这可是家庭聚会
since this is just for family.
我们的老邻居杰瑞是不是
Isn't that our old neighbor, Jerry,
正在往自封袋里装前菜
stuffing appetizers into a ziplock?
雷纳  我们很欢迎你留下
You know what, Rainer, you are more than welcome to stay.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧  我觉得最重要的是
Okay, well, I guess the main thing
邓菲家的人都能齐聚在此
is all the Dunphys are here.
雷纳  明天天气会怎样
Hey, Rainer, what's the weather going to be like for tomorrow?
晴空万里  温度最高在23摄氏度左右
Clear and sunny skies, highs in the mid 70s,
但伞还是不能忘了  因为周一...
but hang onto that umbrella 'cause Monday...
我只想知道明天的
Yeah, I just needed tomorrow,
因为明天是我们的家庭橄榄球赛
because that's when we're having our big family football game.
还记得去年吗
Remember last year?
我们用的那战术
We ran that play?
海利式超远长传
The Haley Mary?
可是明天我们...
Uh, but tomorrow we're supposed...
预计是晴天吗  你说过了
To have sunny weather? Yeah, you said that.
雷纳周末要带我去卡波
Rainer's taking me to Cabo for the weekend.
卡波圣卢卡斯  墨西哥海边度假胜地
所以我有个问题
So, I had a problem.
我不知道我的吹风机
I wasn't sure if my hairdryer
用墨西哥的电还能不能运转
ran on Mexican electricity.
还有  要怎么告诉我爸
Oh, and telling my dad.
我有两个问题了
I had two problems.
医生把这称为"癔病性阳痿"
Doctor's call it "Hysterical impotence."
就是说身体上没毛病
There's nothing physically wrong, per se.
但因为我离婚的创伤
But because of my divorce trauma,
可能影响到了我下面的小兄弟
I guess I'm rewired down there.
-我懂了  -时髦都市人
- I get it. - Okay, city slickers,
猜猜谁家后院里有个真正的爱畜乐园
guess who has a genuine petting zoo in the backyard?
* 夏日微风  让我舒爽 *
* Summer breeze makes me feel fine *
瞧瞧
All right!
好多动物
Animals!
卡梅隆  你还做了个长得像米奇的稻草人
Oh, Cam, and you had the scarecrow made to look like Mitch!
不不不  那稻草人是我妈从老家寄来的
No, no, no, my mom sent that out from Missouri.
他从小伴着我长大
I grew up with that.
我连跳舞都是跟他学的呢
I even learned how to dance with it.
但经你这么一说  我貌似是有个理想型
I guess, now that you mention it, I do have a-a type.
-那只山羊头上是啥  -我的伟大创意
- Hey, what's on this goat's head? - That's my big idea --
摄相机记录下大伙的快乐时光
a camera to capture everyone's delight!
-猜猜我管这叫啥  -羊动专业摄影吗
- Guess what I call it. - Goat-Pro?
音似此类运动专业摄影机GoPro
你取的这名字...  也不赖
That's also a...good name, yep.
看啊  乔  这是一只山羊
Look, Joe. This is a goat.
我好害怕
Ahh, I'm scared!
不不不  没什么好害怕的
No, no, no, there's nothing to be scared of.
它就是这么跟别人说"我爱你"
That's the way he says, "I love you."
这么多动物之中  这货的叫声
Of all the animals, this one is the one
跟告密者在被施以极刑时的惨叫最像
that sounds the most like an informer being tortured.
我不能再有一个怕动物的儿子
I cannot have another son that is afraid of animals.
曼尼五岁时  他去爱畜乐园玩
When Manny was 5, he went to a petting zoo
双肩包里装满了松露爆米花
with a backpack full of truffle popcorn.
在人们终于把那些猪从他身上拽下来时
By the time they pulled the pigs off him,
他全身上下只剩一只袜子了
he was only wearing one sock.
乔  放心
Joe, relax.
动物不会无故攻击人类的
Animals don't attack people for no reason.
放开我  快点放开
Let go of me! Oh, let go of me!
快逃  杰瑞  他们可会欺负人了
Run, Jerry! They do terrible things!
好消息
Good news.
我们提前寄出的洗发产品包裹
The box of hair products we pre-shipped has arrived
已经抵达度假村了
and is waiting for us at the resort.
我不在乎我们的头发了
I don't care about our hair anymore.
你这是在胡言乱语
Hey! That's crazy talk.
我还是没足够的勇气告诉我父母
I still haven't gotten up the guts to tell my parents.
我妈也许能接受  但我爸一定会抓狂
My mom will be cool, but my dad is gonna freak out.
那我去告诉他
Well, I'll tell him.
我和你爸是好哥们
Your dad and I are buds.
而且我特擅长跟人说坏消息的同时保持微笑
And I am excellent at delivering bad news with a smile.
这意味着海岸巡防队员
And that means the Coast Guard
能回家与家人一同度过假期
will be spending the holidays with their families,
因为此次搜索行动已被叫停
because the search has been called off.
你果然厉害
Wow, you're good.
菲尔  你好
Phil. Hey.
我知道最近我们一直聚少离多
I know we haven't been spending enough time together lately,
但我在卡波预约了超赞的度假别墅过周末
but I scored this amazing villa in Cabo for the weekend,
我想带个特殊的人一起去
and I wanted to take a special someone.
我在听
Listening.
我知道你有家庭橄榄球大赛
I know you have your big family football game,
但别墅紧临大海  可以在海滩上骑马
but it's right on the water. Horseback riding on the beach.
我已经看见我俩穿白衬衫策马奔腾了
I see us both in white shirts.
-菲尔  -克莱尔  我知道
- Phil. - Claire, I know.
听起来像是我一生中最美好的周末  我的朋友
It sounds like the best weekend of my life, mi amigo,
但我不能去  要享受家庭时光
but I can't. It's family time.
-他是想带海莉去  -没错
- He wants to take Haley. - Yeah.
你以为我在邀请你吗
Did you think I was asking you?
咋啦  作为好哥们不能逗逗你玩吗
What... brother can't yank a brother's chain?
小题大做想搞事啊
You trippin'?
哥们真逗
This guy!
我会给你发些照片的
I'll send you some pictures.
-好啊  -但在裸体沙滩拍的就不发了
- Okay. - But not from the nude beach. Ooh!
真好笑因为裸体的是我的宝贝女儿
Oh, that's funny 'cause it's my naked daughter!
而你把她从我身边夺走了
And you're taking her away!
不哭不哭
It's okay.
看见没  它们很喜欢被你抚摸
See? They like it when you pet them.
如果你凝视着它们的眼睛
And when you look into their eyes,
就会发现它们其实很聪明
you can see that they're very smart.
它们也有内心和灵魂
They have a very deep soul.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
一只山羊还要什么名字  让你摸你就摸
Name? It's a goat. Just touch it.
我知道海莉去卡波让你很郁闷
I know it's a bummer, Haley going to Cabo.
她去不去还不一定呢
I wouldn't salt those margarita glasses just yet.
等我让她记起家里的感恩节周末多好玩
Once I remind her how much fun Thanksgiving weekend is here,
她就哪也不想去了
she's not going anywhere.
希望效果会好过你上次那个
Well, I hope it goes better than
"白雪溜冰团比科切拉音乐节更酷"的
your big presentation on why the Ice Capades
推销大作战
were cooler than Coachella.
宝贝
Hey, honey.
我听说你们计划着要去旅行
I heard you had some tentative travel plans.
其实我们刚刚在网上确认了航班
Actually, we just checked in for our flight online.
谢谢你在这件事上这么开明
Thanks for being so cool about this.
当然
Of course. Mmm.
有饮用水真好
Potable water.
咱美国人都对干净的水源习以为常了对吧
We take this stuff for granted stateside, don't we?
我们去的是五星级度假村
It's a five-star resort.
我很肯定水会很干净的
I'm sure we'll be fine.
闻闻那些小吃的香气
Smell those side dishes.
等到明天赛前野餐时
They're gonna be even better tomorrow
味道肯定更好
at the post-game picnic.
你知道有什么不像野餐一样放松吗
You know what's not a picnic?
在卧室里穿上拖鞋时
Putting on your bedroom slipper
发现脚上爬满了蝎子
and getting an ankle full of scorpion.
谢了  老爸  我愿意冒这个险
Thanks, Dad. I'll take my chances.
你上次去科切拉音乐节前也是这么说的
That's what you said about Coachella,
而你错过了克丽斯蒂·山口和小蟋蟀杰明尼
and you missed Kristi Yamaguchi doing a triple twist lift
克丽斯蒂·山口为美国著名花样滑冰选手
做转体三周托举
with Jiminy Cricket.
-怎么了  -你血压那么高不能吃这个
- What? - You are not allowed to eat those with your blood pressure.
别担心  这些薯片的影响
Don't worry. These chips won't show up
几周后才能看出来  到时我已经换医生了
for a couple of weeks, and by then I'll have switched doctors.
不好意思  歌洛莉亚下令了
Sorry, Gloria's orders.
杰  看起来你需要跳跳方块舞放松一下
Hey, Jay, looks like you could use a little square dance.
那是我最不想做的...
That would be about the last...
* 拉住你的舞伴  转个圈 *
* Ho, grab your partner, swing 'em 'round *
* 换上最好的衣裳  进城逛 *
* Put on your best suit and go to town *
小卡  你为什么
Cam, why are you...
* 吃点玉米  把马骑 *
* Eat some corn and ride a horse *
* 问俺们爽不  当然爽 *
* Are we having fun? Why, yes, of course *
够了  我要走人了
That's it! I'm out of here!
我要去药房买点阿司匹林
I need some aspirin. I'm going to a pharmacy.
我也去  没什么理由
I'm coming too. No reason.
这年头抛下家人貌似是不需要理由的
Apparently, you don't need a reason to leave your family.
我也去  我的方便面和抗抑郁药不够了
I'll go too. I'm out of ramen and Xanax.
这是什么情况
What's happening?
我们天气预报圈里管这叫
This is what we in the weather game
"高压[力]系统"
refer to as a "High-pressure system."
此情此景让我想起
This reminds me of the time
我撞见你边看《壮志凌云》边"撸黄油棍"
I walked in on you watching "Top Gun".
你别再提起那件事了
You need to stop telling that story.
无论你对小卡做了什么
Whatever you did to Cam,
肯定没糟到那份上
it can't have been that bad.
也肯定不值得你这么牺牲
And it is not worth this.
也许你是对的  也许我过于担忧了
Maybe you're right. Maybe I'm worrying too much.
没错
You are.
我把小卡的费兹波小丑服送人了
I gave Cam's Fizbo costume away.
我的天  这里即将发生灭门惨案
Oh, my God, he's gonna kill everyone in the house.
当时卡车已经到了  各种纸箱子混在一起
The truck was here, and there were so many boxes,
你也知道我一扔旧货就会兴奋得昏了头
and you know how excited I get about a deduction.
听我说
Listen to me.
他不会相信那只是意外的
He's not going to believe that this was an accident.
你永远永远不能告诉他
You can never, ever tell him.
他会发现衣服不见了的
He's gonna know it's missing.
屁大点活动他都要拿出来穿
I mean, he pulls it out for everything.
生日派对  早午餐  高温瑜珈
Birthday parties, brunches, hot yoga...
我得等到时机对了再说
I-I need to wait for the right moment.
时机永远也不会对的
There's not gonna be a right moment.
每当我抱着小猪崽
Hey, ain't nothing in the world that can get me down
这世上再也没有什么能把我打倒了
when I'm holding a little piglet.
看看她
Look at her!
是时候了  亲爱的
It's time. Sweetie?
-不要  -不要什么
- Don't do it. - Don't do what?
我需要你坐下听
I need you to sit down for this.
坐在草包上
Take a bale.
想想孩子们
Think of the children.
莉莉  德怀特
Lily, Dwight.
我把菲茨宝送人了
I gave Fizbo away.
-什么  -我知道那套衣服对你意义深远
- What? - I know how much that costume meant to you,
我真的非常非常抱歉
and I am so, so sorry.
这需要好好消化
Well, it's a lot to process.
我理解人难免会犯错
I know. Accidents do happen.
而且我正抱着一只小猪崽
And I am holding a little piglet.
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
如果你们不介意的话  我要去油炸火鸡了
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a turkey to deep fry.
给  抱着康纳
Here. Hold Connor.
-不...好吧
- No, I... Okay.
我嫁给了这个星球上
I married the sweetest,
最温柔最善解人意的男人
most understanding man on the planet.
或者他对你做了甚至更糟糕的事情
Or he did something even worse to you
只想让你有个好心情
and wants to get you in a good mood.
不会的
No.
肯定是
Yes!
你不用遮住你的脸
You don't have to cover your face.
我不在乎小卡教练说的传染性接吻病
I don't care what Coach Cam says about mono.
而且你的可爱我没抵抗力
You're way too pretty.
别这么说
Oh, no.
我有些受宠若惊
I mean, listen, I'm flattered,
但虽然你长这么  那么高
but even though you are so, so tall
你还在上高中  而我
you are in high school and I'm...
超美
Very beautiful.
好吧
Well...
我本来要说上大学  但还是谢谢你
I was going to say, "in college," but thanks.
别这样  天哪
Stop it, oh, my God!
爸爸要把我逼死了
Ugh! Dad is killing me.
他企图让我感到愧疚然后不去卡波
He's trying to guilt trip me out of going to Cabo.
他什么时候才能让我过自己的生活
When is he gonna let me live my own life?
也许等你不再住在他的地下室
Maybe when you stop living out of his basement
不再吃他的东西时
and eating all of his food.
你说得对  我就是受害者
You're right. I am a victim.
我该买这个迷你漱口水给海莉
I should get this tiny mouthwash for Haley.
这是抛弃家人去旅行装
It's the abandon-your-family travel size.
我的天
Oh, dear God.
我知道  炸玉米粒  这时候在买一送一
I know -- Corn Nuts, two-for-one sale.
我感觉上帝在对我竖中指
I feel like God's giving me the middle finger.
不  那是我妻子的离婚律师
No. That's my wife's divorce lawyer.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
那个混蛋也是我前妻的律师
That bastard was my ex's lawyer.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
我打赌他是来这买超小号避孕套
I bet he's here to buy some extra-small condoms,
需要找药剂师买的那种
the kind that they keep behind the counter.
少啰嗦
Shut up.
我一直做梦他快要渴死在沙漠里
I keep having this dream that he's dying of thirst
然后我开车撞飞他
in the desert, and I hit him with my car.
-我以为你已经走出来了  -我本来也以为
-I thought you were over it. -I thought I was.
趁我的手铐还没炸开  我们快走吧
Let's get out of here before my cuff explodes.
他已经毁了我的家庭
Yeah, he already ruined my family.
我不想他再毁了我的感恩节
I don't want him to ruin my Thanksgiving too.
不
No.
我们哪也不去
We're not going anywhere.
是时候有人站出来
It's time someone stood up
对抗那些堂而皇之闯进我们生活
to the weasels who sweep into our lives,
破坏我们家庭
break up our families,
带走我们挚爱去卡波的黄鼠狼了
and take our loved ones to Cabo.
我感觉你在把事扯到自己身上  但你说得对
I feel like you're making this about you, but you're right.
你知道我什么时候开始有高血压的吗
Do you know when my high blood pressure started?
从我遇到那个人开始
When I met that guy.
这时候是不是该有人说  "把他拿下"
Is this when someone's supposed to say, "Get him!"
-不  -你把他按住
- No. - You hold him down.
我来用这只矫形鞋打他
I'm gonna beat him with this orthopedic shoe.
-来吧  -我们别想出第一个主意就行动啊
- Come here! - Let's not lock into our -- our first idea.
我爱你  山羊先生
I love you, Mr. Goat!
你看  乔
Aw, you see, Joe?
听妈妈的话  现在你就有新朋友了
You listen to Mommy, and now you have a new best friend.
什么
What?
你冷  我去给你拿条毯子
You're cold? I'll go get you a blanket!
如果他是去给猪拿毯子
Well, if he was going to get the pig a blanket,
你们知道应该怎么称呼吗
you know what that would be called.
猪包毯吗
Pig in a blanket?
一种以香肠为主菜的配菜佳肴  状似热狗面包
好吧  这哏我也算喂到你嘴边了
Okay, I teed that one up for you.
好了  该炸火鸡了
All right, it's time to fry this turkey.
你俩谁能来帮我把防溅护目镜放下来
Somebody please lower my splatter goggles, boys?
叫你呢
You heard him.
你去
You do it.
你又不是放眼镜主席  随便使唤人
You're not the president of goggle lowering.
如果有办投票我就能当
I would be if they took a vote.
小卡能做错什么呢
What could Cam have done?
也许是他出轨了
Maybe he's the one who's having an affair.
我在杂志上看过出轨征兆
I saw a list of clues in a magazine.
他最近有没有加健身房会员或者买性感内衣
Has he joined a gym or bought sexy new underwear recently?
很感谢看得起我们
I think it's sweet that you think
觉得我们还有余力出轨  但我们真的很累
we're capable of having an affair, but we're just so tired.
好了各位
All right now, boys,
一定要像这样轻轻地慢慢地放下去
the key is you drop it nice and gentle like.
接吻病
Mono!
脱缰之羊
Runaway goat!
你是想躲去畜棚吧
Aw, you wanted to run to the barn!
我来反转一下这个悲伤的故事
Let me put a positive spin on this.
谁喜欢吃羊肉
Who here likes goat?
你这个畜生
Hello, you son of a bitch.
希望那个除臭剂好用  因为你就是个臭家伙
Hope you like that deodorant, 'cause you stink!
退疣灵
Wart remover --
见效的话  你全身就要不见了
well, if that works, there'll be nothing left.
哎哟哟  诺伯特和普里契特
Well, well, well. Norbert and Pritchett.
杰  一直没机会向你道谢
Jay, I don't think I ever got a chance
多谢你让我赚进了第一辆法拉利
to thank you for buying me my first Ferrari.
祝你开下悬崖
I wish you drove it off a cliff.
我的豪宅就在悬崖上
Like the one my house is on,
也是用你的钱买的  太感谢了
which you also paid for, thank you?
我们不是要把他拿下的吗
This doesn't sound like we're getting him.
你们想要免费法律建议吗  伙计们
Look, you want some free legal advice, fellas?
送你们三个词  娘们  滚吧  废柴
Three words -- Ladies. Leave. Losers.
不  先生  我们有三个字送你
No, sir, we have three words for you.
你 有没 羞...
Have you no sh-- have you --
没有...  没羞没躁  四个字
have no -- have you no shame -- it can be four words.
这傻蛋是谁
Who's this chuckle-head?
你永远也不会认识的人
Someone who you're never gonna know,
因为我结婚以来大部分时间都很幸福
'cause I'm happily married most of the time.
大家都这么说
Aw, that's what they all say.
然后有一天你老婆醒了之后说  "我的天
Then one day your wife wakes up and says, "Oh, my God!
我嫁了个傻逼"
I married a moron!"
她给我打电话  我接起来说
She calls me, and I'm like,
"你好  傻蛋夫人..."
"Hello, Mrs. Chuckle--"
挺准的
Yeah, that's about right.
他可能是心脏病发了
He might have had a heart attack.
我们好像该做点什么吧
We probably ought to do something.
我之前有看到那边有香槟
Oh, I saw some champagne back there.
他倒这儿了
It's the guy on the ground!
拿着除颤器  我去报警
Oh! Take the defibrillator, I'll call 911.
两位帮帮我  我根本不会用这个
Guys, help me out. I don't know what I'm doing.
我看了好多《实习医生格蕾》
I watch a lot of "Grey's Anatomy,"
不过所有不浪漫的镜头我全快进了
but I fast-forward through the non-romantic scenes.
不不不  不能救他
No no no, we're not gonna save him!
杰瑞  别这样  杰瑞
Jerry, no, Jerry.
杰  把他拉开
Jay, get him off me!
看看他的购物篮  活得也不是舒适
Look at his basket. Wasn't much of a life.
天啊  我肯定会后悔的
Ah, hell, I'm gonna regret this.
我感觉好点了  普里契特  应该只是胀气
I'm feeling better, Pritchett. I think it was just gas.
以防万一
Better safe than sorry.
一部分错在我
Oh, I deserve some of the blame.
我把农场风情画弄得太有吸引力了
I made my farmscape too inviting.
好吧  简直一团糟
Okay. This is a mess.
我们要怎么办
What are we gonna do now?
艾丽克斯  需要牺牲多少条羊命
Alex, how many goats have to die
你才能停止对高中小鲜肉
until you get a handle on your insatiable appetite
无休止的渴望
for high-school boys?
其实  这是我的错
Actually, I-it's my fault.
德怀特  我们长得好看的人
Ooh, Dwight. We're good-looking guys.
不为自己有吸引力而道歉
We don't apologize for it.
我把毯子拿来了  山羊先生
I got you a blanket, Mr. Goat.
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no!
我们去烟囱旁边等圣诞老人
We're going to wait for Santa Claus by the chimney!
但今天是感恩节啊
But it's Thanksgiving.
山羊先生怎么办
What about Mr. Goat?
为什么我听不到他的声音了
How come I don't hear him anymore?
山羊先生没事啦
Ay, Mr. Goat is fine!
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
你说什么  山羊先生
What is it, Mr. Goat?
他说他想静静
He's saying that he needs some time alone.
看  这些是给圣诞老人的饼干
Look, there's some cookies for Santa.
给你  去烟囱边坐着等好吗
Here, why don't you go and sit by the chimney and wait.
圣诞老人
Santa!
我不应该插嘴你孩子的教育
Hey lookit, it's not my place to try to parent your kids.
-很好  -但是我们在农场上学到的就是
- Good. - But one thing we learn on the farm
死亡是生命的一部分
is that death is a part of life.
你敢告诉乔那只山羊出事了
If you tell Joe what happened to that goat,
死亡将会是你生命的一部分
death is gonna be part of your life.
其实孩子的承受能力比你想象中要大得多
You know what, kids can handle a lot more than you think.
而且从出生到死亡的每一步
And every step, from birth till the end,
都有它自身的魅力
has its own magical beauty.
是要把山羊塞进垃圾桶里
So, do we jam the goat in the garbage
还是扔到围栏外
or heave it over the fence?
好好教你的孩子吧
Teach your children well.
谢谢你刚刚救了我
Hey. Thanks for before.
推了我一把  免得被山羊撞上
You know, pushing me out of the way of the goat.
不用谢啦
Don't worry about it.
为了保护领导人而已
It's more about protecting the office.
我们都知道应该是你当主席的
Look, I think we both know you should have been president.
或许我一直找你麻烦是因为我嫉妒你
Maybe I've been hard on you 'cause I'm jealous.
好呀
Yeah, okay.
我在搬这死羊  你俩却在这里谈情说爱
You two keep making out while I carry the dead goat.
山羊先生
Mr. Goat?
电话账单上有什么可疑活动吗
Any suspicious activity on that phone bill?
小卡花了100刀打通灵热线
Well, Cam spent $100 on the psychic hotline...
但是赛季越来越紧张时  这也是正常的
...but that's normal during the run-up to award's season.
我刚看到南瓜酱快吃完了
I just saw we were running out of pumpkin dip,
我知道你最喜欢这个  就给你拿了点过来
and I know it's your favorite, so I brought you some.
你到底在玩什么把戏
What's your game?
-没错  亮出你内衣里的乾坤  -什么
- Yeah, show us your underwear. - What?
菲茨宝的事情你为什么这么淡定
Why are we so understanding about Fizbo, huh?
你在隐瞒什么
What are you hiding?
隐瞒
Hiding?
你太可耻了
Shame on you.
今天是感恩节
It's Thanksgiving.
我想跟我的丈夫
I want to celebrate with my husband,
我的女儿  我可爱的家人  杰瑞一起庆祝
my daughter, my lovely family, Jerry.
你们俩把生活看作是一场
I think it's sad that you two look at life
每个人都试着摆脱某些事责任的游戏
as some sort of game where everyone's trying
真是太可悲了
to get away with something.
有的人就是人很好而已
Some people are just nice.
他们信了
They bought it.
其实是我把我们之前
Truth is, I paid for the jamboree
为了去夏威夷度假省下的钱花在这场欢宴上
with money we had saved for a romantic Hawaiian vacation.
我甚至还从密苏里买了奢华草包寄过来
I even sprung for fancy straw bales flown in from Missouri.
这才叫档次
That's class.
这里出什么事了
The hell happened here?
我这一天也是受够了
I think I felt enough for one day.
可能是我被电击太多的副作用
It's possible I've been electrocuted one too many times.
我今天学到了一些东西
You know, I learned something today.
我看到一个人在我面前差点死了
I saw a man nearly die right in front of me.
而这玩意时刻在提醒我
And this is a constant reminder
我也随时可能有同样遭遇
that it can happen to me at any moment.
很让人不禁思考
It's a lot to think about.
所以老子不戴了
So I'm not gonna.
菲尔  给我拿瓶啤酒
Phil, get me a beer.
杰瑞  给我来杯威士忌
Jerry, get me a scotch.
我今天也有点心得
I learned something today, too.
现在不是时候  杰瑞
It's a lot right now, Jerry.
出什么事了  儿子
What's the matter, kid?
我爱山羊先生
I loved Mr. Goat.
它死了
He died.
求你别抽了
Please don't smoke.
你完全不需要担心  乔
Hey, don't you worry about a thing, Joey.
我会一直在
I'm not going anywhere.
爸  不管你说什么  卡波我去定了
Dad, I don't care what you say. I'm going to Cabo.
行  去吧
You sure are.
对对对  我会被阿兹特克人绑架
Sure, I'm gonna get kidnapped by Aztecs
已灭绝的墨西哥古文明  存在于14至16世纪
然后扔进火山里献祭  行了
and sacrificed in a volcano. I get it.
不  宝贝  我想要你去
No, honey, I want you to go.
抱歉我之前那样子
I-I'm sorry about earlier.
我很生气  但没有直接说
I was mad. And instead of talking about it,
死憋在心里  结果爆发反而更难看
I pushed it down and it came out in some ugly ways
伤到我美丽的女儿和那个长疣的律师
with my beautiful daughter and a lawyer who has warts.
总之  只是因为你的生活
Anyway, it's just more and more of your life
越来越与我无关  这很正常  也是好事
is happening away from me, and it's normal and good,
但我难以接受
but it's hard.
靠  你这么贴心干嘛
Damn it, why do you have to be so sweet?
现在我感觉内疚了
Now I feel guilty.
别内疚  去卡波好好玩
Don't. Go to Cabo. Have fun.
我可以今天玩橄榄球
You know, I could play football today.
来一次海利式超远长传战术
Run that Haley Mary?
那就太好了
That would be so wonderful...
-又被电了吗  -很严重
- Electrocuted again? - Real bad.
散开  上吧
Okay, break! Let's go!
好了  大家
All right, everybody.
欢迎来到第15届感恩节橄榄球年度比赛
Welcome to the 15th annual Thanksgiving football game,
这次提前一天举行
being played a day early.
我必须提一句
I'd be remiss if I didn't mention
我们能齐聚一堂真是太棒了
how beautiful it is that we're all together.
是我的错觉吗  还是你们也能感受到爱...
Is it just me, or can you feel the love...
-能快点开始吗  -好吧
- Can we please do this? - All right.
准备进攻
Down!
就位
Set.
-菲尔  我们还好吧  -很好
- Phil, we're good, right? - Oh, we're great.
你真该带克莱尔去一次这个度假村
You should really take Claire to this resort.
超浪漫
Very romantic.
蓝色39号战术
Blue, 39!
每个房间都有心形浴缸
Heart-shaped jacuzzi in every room.
堪萨斯城  堪萨斯城
Kansas City, Kansas City...
其实  我现在才算很好
Actually, now I'm great.
天哪  老爸  要这样吗
Oh, my God, Dad. Seriously?
真是美好的一天
Ah, what a beautiful day.
我累坏了
Oh, I am exhausted.
我已经在为夏威夷之旅倒数了
I'm counting down the days till we're in Hawaii.
亲爱的  我估计你得数好久好久了
Sweetie, I don't know if you can count that high.
还记得我对菲茨宝这事多淡定吗
You remember how cool I was with the whole Fizbo thing?
小卡  你把夏威夷经费花这派对上了吧
Cam, you spent the Hawaii money on this party, didn't you?
我们这是怎么了
What is wrong with us?
从现在起  我们要互相坦诚  好吗
From now on, can we just be honest with each other, all right?
-不耍心计  -成交
- No more games. - Deal.
爸爸们  你们看着很累
Hey, daddies. You look tired.
我给你们做了烤芝士三明治
I made you some grilled cheese sandwiches.
爱你们
Love you.
-我们还是有做得好的地方  -是啊
- Well, there's something we did right. - Yeah.
我得保持他们心情好
I needed them in a good mood.
我留下了爱畜乐园的鸡
I kept this from the petting zoo.
仅纪念德洛丽丝·莱维坦
[这位女士是《摩登家庭》制作人的母亲]
一键收藏网盘资源生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）